1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser(URL)
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
33. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. setText(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), "IPHONE 11 PRO 128 GB DEEP PURPLE")
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
45. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-11-pro"))
49. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product"))
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
57. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
61. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
65. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/btn_checkout"))
69. click(findTestObject("Checkout/btn_checkout"))
73. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), 10)
77. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/field_email"), randomEmail)
81. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkout guest/btn_continue"))
85. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_First Name"), 10)
89. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
93. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
97. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_mobile phone"), randomPhone)
101. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/field_Address"), randomAddress)
105. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
109. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_Province"))
113. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
117. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_Select Province"))
121. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/li_Khan Chamkar Mon_Select_Province"))
125. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/input_Districts"))
129. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/li_Sangkat Tonle Basak_Districts"))
133. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn-save"))
137. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing address same as shipping"))
141. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/field_First Name"), 10)
145. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/field_First Name"), randomFirstName)
149. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/field_Last Name"), randomLastName)
153. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/field_mobile phone"), randomPhone)
157. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/field_Address"), randomAddress)
161. setText(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/input_ZipPostal Code"), randomCode)
165. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/input_Province"), 5)
169. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/input_Province"), 10)
173. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/input_Province"))
177. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"), 10)
181. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/li_Phnom Penh Capital_Province"))
185. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/input_Select Province"), 10)
189. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/input_Select Province"))
193. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/li_Khan Mean Chey_1"), 10)
197. mouseOver(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/li_Khan Mean Chey"))
201. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/li_Khan Mean Chey_1"))
205. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/input_Districts"), 10)
209. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/input_Districts"))
213. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/li_Sangkat Chak Angrae Kraom"), 10)
217. mouseOver(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/li_Sangkat Chak Angrae Kraom"))
221. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/Billing/li_Sangkat Chak Angrae Kraom_1"))
225. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Online Payment - WeChat"))
229. check(findTestObject("Checkout/Checkbox__I accept"))
233. click(findTestObject("Checkout/btn_checkout"))
237. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/iframe_payment_online"), 10)
241. click(findTestObject("Checkout/iframe_payment_online"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
245. delay(10)
249. click(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Approve"))
253. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Continue shopping"), 10)
257. verifyElementPresent(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Continue shopping"), 0)
261. click(findTestObject("Checkout/button_Continue shopping"))
265. takeScreenshot()
269. comment("Email      : " + randomEmail)
273. comment("First Name : " + randomFirstName)
277. comment("Last Name  : " + randomLastName)
281. comment("Phone      : " + randomPhone)
285. comment("Address    : " + randomAddress)
289. comment("Code    : " + randomCode)
293. closeBrowser()